Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 62, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Oxygen Therapy Service to Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: Personnel Services
  - Item 7: Oxygen Therapy Service To Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Policy-Medical Services to Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Procedure- Medical Services to Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Military Training Policy - U.S. Only, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Policy for Employees Who Enter United States Military Service, 1950; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: Leave of Absence
  - Item 12: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Employee Participation in Military Programs, 1956; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Time Off for Voting, 1955; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Interview: Mr. W.H. Winans, Miss Eleanor Park, Mr. Haas, and Mr. Mason, industrial relations staff at head-quarters, Union Carbide & Carbon Corporation, N.Y., 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: Confidential
  - Item 24: Naynes Stellite Company, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Notes: A Division of Union Carbide and Carbon Corporation
- Box: 62, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees at Atomic Energy Installations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Hospital Expense and Surgical Operation Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: For Hourly Employees of Bakelite Company
  - Item 3: Hospital Expense and Surgical Operation Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Hospital Expense and Surgical Operation Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: Electro Metallurgical Company
  - Item 5: Major Medical Expense Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Dental Expense Assistance Plan, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Group Insurance Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: Hourly Employees
  - Item 8: Hospitalization and Surgical Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Hospital Surgical Medical, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Hospitalization and Surgical Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Group Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Group Insurance Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Pension Benefits and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: Under Non-Contributory Pension Plan for Employees
  - Item 15: The Pension Plan, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Pension Benefits and Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Retirement Plan for Employees in the United States, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: The Pension Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Pension Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: National Carbon Company, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: History Products Organization
  - Item 21: About Carbide, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: "The Carbide", Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: A Pioneer Industry of the Sea
  - Item 23: Your Union Carbide Group Insurance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Notes: Salaried Employees
  - Item 24: Historical Summary, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Application for Clerical Position, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: Employement Application, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Box: 62, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Orientation for Employes, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Procedure for Recruiting, Placement and Training of New Engineers, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Schedule of Orientation Visits for New Accountants, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Retirement Plan for Employes, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Retirement Plan for Employes, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Represented by Local 148, I.U.O.E. and the International Union of Operating Engineers
  - Item 6: Retirement Plan for Employes, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Represented by Locals 309, 649 and 1439, I.B.E.W. and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
  - Item 7: Retirement Plan for Employes, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Represented by Locak 1455, I.B.E.W. and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
  - Item 8: You and Union Electric: A Handbook for Employes, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Building for Your Future, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Union Electric Company Retirement Plan
  - Item 10: Notice of Vacancy Subject to Bidding Procedure, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Letter to Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Herbert W. Loeh
  - Item 12: Routines for Posting and Filling Jobs at Union Electric, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Industrial Relations Organization, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Union Electric Company Employee Relations, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Union Electric Company Employee Relations, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Orientation Program for New Assistant Engineers: Group No. 5, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Introduction of New Employees, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Earl F. Voelz
  - Item 19: Organization Changes, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: E. K. Dille
    Notes: Union Electric Company Power Operations
  - Item 20: Tuition Refund Application, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: You Are Union Electric, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: The Good Sense of Human Relations, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Public Opinion
  - Item 23: Application for Employment, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Union Electric System
  - Item 24: Rough Cost Estimating, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Motor Vehicle Operator Training, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Handbook: "More Power for All"
  - Item 26: Training Programs, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Television and Training, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Typical Schedule: Assistan Engineer Training Program, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Your Use of Television for Training, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: Subjects Used To Date Management Development Program Union Electric Company of Missouri, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Baisc Training for Supervisors, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: Explanation of Single Phase Distribution Transformer The Lightning Arrester, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Training Program Transmission and Distribution Div.- Overhead Construction
  - Item 33: Reddy in the Firing Line, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: Salary Policy, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Charles J. Dougherty
  - Item 35: Union Electric Employe Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: Supplementary Group Life Insurance Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: A Plan of Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Expense Insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: for Retired Employees of Union Electric Company
  - Item 38: Second Boiler Hydrostatic Tested, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Notes: Meramec Progress Vol IV, No.2
  - Item 39: Orientation, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Box: 62, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Facsimile of Illustrated Guide, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Notes: Orientation Program
  - Item 2: Basic Supervision Course No. 1: Schedules, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Basic Supervision Course Group No. 107, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Authorization of Payroll Deduction for Advanced Tuition, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Educational Programs and Services, 1966; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Educational Department Concept and Functions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Retirement Counseling Booklet, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Union Electric Company Employers' Savings and Stock Subscriptions Plan, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Customer Business: "CustomersAnd You", Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: "The Court of Human Relations", 1950; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: Thomas J. French
- Box: 62, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employe Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Guides to Your Safety, Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: A Plan of Group Major Medical Expense Insurance for Employes of Unio Electric Company, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: A Plan of Group Insurance, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Notes: for Employes of Union Electric Company of Missouri, Union Electric Power Company, St. Louis & Belleville Electric Railway Company
  - Item 5: A Plan of Group Insurance for Employes of Union Electric Company of Missouri, 1955; Publication (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Box: 62, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employe Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 62, Folder 13)
    Author: K. Streett
- Box: 62, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan Highlights, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Medical Protection, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Retirement Income, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Income Protection, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Life Insurance, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Profitable Retirement, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Author: George W. Craigie
    Notes: Published for the Employees ofUnion Oil Company of California
  - Item 8: Protection for You and Yours: Think Safety, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Insured Medical Plan for Employees and Dependents, 1955; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Employees Incentive Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Employees Medical Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Disability Income Plan Highlights, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Life Insurance Plan Highlights, Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Working Together: A Handbook for Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Box: 62, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Fire Protection Training Notes Basic, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Stretching For Safety, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Defensive Driving Pays: How to Win the Safe Driver Award, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: What Is It, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Brakes Aren't Enough, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Fire Protection Training, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Notes: Los Angeles Refinery
  - Item 7: Objectives and Functions of the Fire and Safety Division of The Industrial Relations Department As Related to Safety, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Fire Protection Papers, Publication (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Box: 62, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Employees Incentive Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Delivering the Finest, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Management - The Development of People, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: The Basic Training Pattern, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Successful Training Follows a Pattern, Publication (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Box: 62, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: An Investment in Tomorrow, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Notes: "A Retirement Program for employees and members of their families"
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Notes: Protection
- Box: 63, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The United Airlines Performance Evaluation Program, 1969; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Managing Employee Ideas, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: Management Guide to Suggestion Evaluation
  - Item 3: Suggestion Program, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: What It Is; How It Works; Why You Benefit
  - Item 4: You and United Air Lines, 1962; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Employees Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Promoting Employee Suggestions, 1962; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Management Training Catalog, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: You and United, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: You and United Air Lines, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Your Insurance as an Employee of United Air Lines, 1955; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: United Air Lines Retirement Program, 1953; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Your Insurance as an Employee of United Air Lines, Inc., Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Employees Stock Plan Authorization, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Personnel and Industrial Relations, 1978; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Industrial Organization, 1978; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Personnel Regions, 1970; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Personnel and Industrial Relations, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Industrial Organization, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Industrial Organization, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Industrial Relations Organization, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: Personnel
  - Item 21: United Air Lines Long Term Disability Insurance Plan for Flight Dispatchers and Assistant Flight Dispatchers, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Employees' Stock Purchase Plan Information, 1962; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: UAL Employees On Military Leave of Absence, 1953; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Explaining Office Policy and Practice to New Employees, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Employees' Stock Purchase Plan Information, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Box: 63, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Management Training, 1955; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1955-56 Announcements
  - Item 2: Mainline Managements Memo, 1957; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: Volume 6 - Number 1
  - Item 3: Employee Development Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Box: 63, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Education Matching Gift Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Notes: of Financial Aid To Colleges and Universities
- Box: 63, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Blue Shield Surgical-Medical Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Notes: Group and Non-Group Enrollment
- Box: 63, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Summary Description of the United Nations Common System of Salaries, Allowances and Other Conditions of Service, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Box: 63, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Your Civil Service Retirement System, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Box: 63, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Retirement Orientation and Counseling Program, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Notes: Personnel Series 1
  - Item 2: Listening Comprehension, 1964; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Notes: Training Guide Series: Manual No. 1
  - Item 3: Speechmaking, 1964; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Notes: Training Guide Series: Manual No. 2
  - Item 4: Steps in Preparing and Delivering an Effective Speech, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Box: 63, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Training and Technology Project, 1970; Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Notes: Listing of Documents and Reports
  - Item 2: Organized Labor's Participation In A Training Experiment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The General Education Development (GED) Program At Training and Technology, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Notes: Training and Technology Report
  - Item 4: Continuance of an Institutional MDTA Program Throughout a Prolonged Strike, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Notes: Training and Technology
  - Item 5: The Effects of a Manpower Training Program on the Personal Lives of Its Graduates, 1970; Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Notes: Training and Technology Project
  - Item 6: Orientation Program for Y-12 Supervisors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Box: 63, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Past and Present, 1950; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Notes: A Story of Apprentice Training in the Skilled TradesSince Colonial Days
  - Item 2: Training Manpower for Defense Production, 1951; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Author: W.F. Patterson
- Box: 63, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Brazil - Labor Union Leader Training Mixed Industry Group, 1961; Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Box: 63, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Aids To Safety, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Office Safety, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Accident Analysis and Remedial Action, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Notes: Student Work Sheet
  - Item 4: Occupational Safety Aid, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Notes: Safety Committee Activities
  - Item 5: Promoting Worker Interest, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Notes: Occupational Safety Aid
  - Item 6: The Development of The Safety Movement, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Safety Training Techniques in The Classroom, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Supervisory Responsibility For Safety, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Conducting a Job Hazard Analysis, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Elements of A Safety Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Elements of a Safety Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Box: 63, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Industrial Safety Series C Leader's Guide, 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: Training Manual No. 75
  - Item 2: Industrial Safety Series B Leader's Guide, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: Training Manual No. 74
  - Item 3: Industrial Safety Series D Leader's Guide, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: Training Manual No. 76
  - Item 4: Industrial Safety Series A Leader's Guide, Publication (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Notes: Training Manual No. 73
- Box: 63, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Electronic Technician An Introduction to Your Job, Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
    Notes: Maintenance Engineering Branch Training BulletinOJT-1
  - Item 2: Guide for Writing Position Descriptions, Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Employee Promotion Appraisal, 1954; Publication (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Box: 63, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Government-Wide Service Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Notes: Administered by Blue Cross and Blue Shield
  - Item 2: Government-Wide Indemnity Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Annual and Sick Leave Regulations for Federal Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Guide to Office, Personal and other Services, 1951; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: House of Representatives, Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Notes: 89th Congress 1st Session Report No. 508
  - Item 6: Survey of Income of Civil Service Annuitants, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Summer Employment in Federal Agencies, 1958; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Notes: Pamphlet 45
  - Item 8: Report on the Federal Employees Occupational Health Program, 1966; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Notes: Memorandum For The President
  - Item 9: Report on The Partial Tuition Reimbursement Plan for Interns and Trainees of the New York State Public Administrative Program, 1958; Publication (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Box: 63, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Communications and Office Skills Training Center, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Developing Management Potential through Appraisal Panels, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: Personnel Management Series No.8
  - Item 3: Better Building Promotion Programs, 1952; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: Personnel Management Series No. 2
  - Item 4: How to Conserve Stenographic and Typic Skills, 1951; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: A Handbook for Supervisors: Personnel Management Series No. 1
  - Item 5: Executive Seminar Center, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Youth Opportunity Campaign - Summer 1966, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: A Report of Training Conducted by Federal Agencies for Non-College Youths during the Summer of 1966
  - Item 7: Youth Opportunity Campaign - Summer 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: A Report of Training Conducted by Federal Agencies for Young Men and Women Summer Employees in 1967
  - Item 8: How Federal Agencies Develop Management Talent, 1953; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: Management Staff Development Series Report No.3
  - Item 9: How Federal Agencies Develop Management Talent, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: A Management Staff Development Series Prepared From Inventory Data Obtained Directly From the Agencies
  - Item 10: The ADP Management Training Center Programs To Be Offered During Fiscal 1967, 1966; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: How Federal Agencies Develop Management Talent, 1953; Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Notes: Federal Security Agency Management Staff Development Series Report No. 2
  - Item 12: The ADP Management Training Center, Publication (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Box: 63, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Interagency Training Programs, 1959; Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: General Management Training Center, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
    Notes: Interagency Training Programs
  - Item 3: General Management Training Center, 1967; Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Financial Management & PPBS Training Center, Publication (Box 63, Folder 16)